

VIKTORIYA KOPTEVA

QA ENGINEER

SUMMARY:

All my life I am engaged in creativity: music, journalism, poetry, theater. These are the types of creativity that activate not only the right hemisphere of the brain, but also the left. I like to think outside the box and think creatively, think a lot and analyze. IT is also creativity. I love various applications, and I would like to put my hand to making sure that a really high-quality product is released on the market, which will be used, which I myself will use. I want to become part of a cool team of specialists with burning eyes. I am sure that my meticulousness, non-standard thinking, perseverance, thoughtfulness, imaginative and analytical thinking will help me find my place in IT.

HARD SKILLS:

- Operating systems MacOs, Windows
- Platforms iOS, Android

Tools&Other:

- Excel, TestRail
- DevTools
- Postman
- SQL
- lira

Basic knowledge about:

- Charles Proxy
- Android Studio

SOFT SKILLS:

- Leadership skills
- Teamwork
- Communicative
- Fast Learner
- Responsible
- Organized

EXPERIENCE:

Texas Chicken fast food

July 2018 - present

Restaurant crew member

Preparation of dishes according to recipes and formulas. Be able to work in all positions of the kitchen. Keeping the room clean and tidy. Working with a cash register.

Beauty salon

06.2017 - 08.2017

Administrator

Recording clients, cleaning and arranging the studio, maintaining social networks: (creating and processing photos, creating posts), purchasing materials, working with the cash desk.

Children's Art School

09.2015 - 08.2017

Accompanist

Filling out the magazine, conducting classes with students, participating in music competitions

EDUCATION:

Belarusian State University, Faculty of Journalism, Minsk

09.2015 - 06.2019

Belarusian State University of Culture and Arts, Theater director

09.2020-present

Education in IT:

- March 2022 June 2022 Online Course QA **Engineer**
- Courses in app Stepik
- Artem Rusov online course "Tester from scratch" Books:
- Roman Savin "Testing dot com"
- Svyatoslav Kulikov- "Software Testing"

English - A2

CONTACTS:



Belarus, Minsk



+375292055123



vika.kopteva1996@gmail.com



Виктория Коптева